A Guide to the William Garber Photograph Collection, 1930-1960
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
- Ikenberry and Garst General Mdse, with people and a car in the front.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0068; 2.5x3.5
- Ikenberry and Garst General Mdse. Diagonal view from across the street.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0069; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0069 .c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0069a; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0069.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0069b; 2.5x3.5
- Jake’s Fountain Service, outside view. Small roadside restaurant with a gas pump in the front.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0070; 2.5x2.5
- Jake’s Fountain Service, outside view from the front. Small roadside restaurant with a gas pump in the front.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0071; 2.5x2.5
- Dominion Lunch Restaurant, diagonal view from across the street. New Market, Va.c. 1940-1950, Image: P0002.01.0072; 4x5
- Inside of Dominion Lunch Restaurant, view of counter and bar stools, with various food items for sale behind the counter. New Market, Va.c. 1940-1950, Image: P0002.01.0073; 4x5
- Inside of Dominion Lunch Restaurant, view of booth tables across from the counter, with a heating furnace in the middle of the room and a jukebox in the background. New Market, Va.c. 1940-1950, Image: P0002.01.0074; 4x5
- Billiard tables inside of Dominion Lunch Restaurant. New Market, Va.c. 1940-1950, Image: P0002.01.0075; 4x5
- Quedens Lunch Billiards, New Market, Va. Diagonal view from the street.c. 1940-1949, Image: P0002.01.0076; 2.5x3.5
- Quedens Lunch Billiards, New Market, Va. Alternate view from the street, with two men sitting on the sidewalk in front.c. 1940-1949, Image: P0002.01.0077; 2.5x3.5
- Inside of Quedens Lunch Billiards, New Market, Va. View from behind the counter in the front of the restaurant, with wooden booths and a pinball machine pictured.c. 1940-1949, Image: P0002.01.0078; 2.5x3.5
- Inside of Quedens Lunch Billiards, New Market, Va. View of the back of the restaurant, with a pinball machine, jukebox, and tables shown.c. 1940-1949, Image: P0002.01.0079; 2.5x3.5
- Inside of Quedens Lunch Billiards, New Market, Va. Front view of the counter, with two men standing underneath the menu.c. 1940-1949, Image: P0002.01.0080; 2.5x3.5
- Roger’s Restaurant, New Market, Va. Storefront view, advertising chicken, steak, and ham dinners.c. 1940-1949, Image: P0002.01.0081; 4x5
- Walter’s Restaurant. Diagonal view from across the street.c. 1940-1950, Image: P0002.01.0082; 2.5x3.5
- Walter’s Restaurant, storefront view. c. 1940-1950, Image: P0002.01.0083; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0083a.
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0083.c. 1940-1950, Image: P0002.01.0083a; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0083.
- Walter’s Restaurant, outside view, with an ABC Dogfood truck driving in front.c. 1940-1950, Image: P0002.01.0084; 2.5x2.5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0084.c. 1940-1950, Image: P0002.01.0084a; 2.5x2.5
- Inside of Walter’s Restaurant. View of counter with men on both sides looking towards the camera. Candy bars, cans of apple sauce, and other items can be seen for sale behind the counter.c. 1940-1950, Image: P0002.01.0085; 4x5
- Inside of Walter’s Restaurant. Similar view to that in P0002.01.0084, but from a different angle.c. 1940-1950, Image: P0002.01.0086; 4x5
- Inside of Walter’s Restaurant, with both the counter and opposite booth tables pictured. c. 1940-1950, Image: P0002.01.0087; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0087c. 1940-1950, Image: P0002.01.0087a; 4x5
- Similar view of P0002.01.0087, except with men sitting at the counter.c. 1940-1950, Image: P0002.01.0088; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0088.c. 1940-1950, Image: P0002.01.0088a; 4x5
- Inside of Walter’s Restaurant, with an alternate view of a man and applesauce display behind the counter.c. 1940-1950, Image: P0002.01.0089; 4x5
- Larry’s Grill Rooms. Potentially a country roadside restaurant with a gas pump in the front. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0090; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0090.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0090a; 4x5
- Lamma Orkney SPS Restaurant, inside view. Racks of bread and table pictured.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0091; 4x5
- Lamma Orkney SPS Restaurant, inside view. Room of small round tables and chairs featured.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0092; 4x5
- Mick or Mack “Cash Talks” grocery store. Harrisonburg, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0093; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0093.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0093a; 4x5
- Inside of Mick or Mack “Cash Talks,” shelves of food pictured with a shopper and an employee.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0094; 4x5
- Inside of Mick or Mack “Cash Talks,” cash register.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0095; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0095.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0095a; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0095.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0095b; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0095.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0095c; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0095.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0095d; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0095.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0095e; 4x5
- Inside of Mick or Mack Cash Talks, view of empty store.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0096; 4x5
- The front of a movie theater advertising air conditioning and a “double show tonite,” diagonal view from across the street.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0097; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0097.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0097a; 2.5x3.5
- Alternate view of the movie theater, with the street included in the photograph.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0098; 2.5x3.5
- The front window of Hodgin’s Store (electronics and sporting goods) in Woodstock, Va. Window advertises National Baseball Week, April 3-10.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0099; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0099.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0099a; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0099.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0099b; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0099.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0099c; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0099.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0099d; 2.5x3.5
- Man sitting at a desk on the phone inside of Hodgin’s Store, Woodstock, Va. Deer head mounted on the war next to a rack of three rifles.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.00100; 2.5x3.5
- Inside Hodgin’s Store, a man showing a rifle to a woman. Woodstock, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0101; 2.5x3.5
- Inside Hodgin’s Store, alternate view of a man showing a rifle to a woman. Woodstock, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0102; 2.5x3.5
- Inside Hodgin’s Store, two men examining a piece of merchandise, possibly a fishing reel. Woodstock, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0103; 2.5x3.5
- Inside Hodgin’s Store, a man showing a woman a 3-in-1 stove, oven, and dishwasher. Woodstock, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0104; 2.5x3.5
- Inside Hodgin’s Store, fishing tackle, outdoor clothing, etc. on display. Woodstock, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0105; 2.5x3.5
- General view of the inside of Hodgin’s Store.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0106; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0106.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0106a; 2.5x3.5
- Storefront view of Ben Franklin Arts and Crafts Store, Woodstock, Va.1949, Image: P0002.01.0107; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0107.1949, Image: P0002.01.0107a; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0107.1949, Image: P0002.01.0107b; 4x5
- Storefront view of Ben Franklin Arts and Crafts Store, from a diagonal angle. Woodstock, Va.1949, Image: P0002.01.0108; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0108.1949, Image: P0002.01.0108a; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0108.1949, Image: P0002.01.0108b; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0108.1949, Image: P0002.01.0108c; 4x5
- Storefront view of Ben Franklin Arts and Crafts Store, from an alternate diagonal angle. Woodstock, Va. 1949, Image: P0002.01.0109; 4x5
- Storefront view of Timberville Department Store, Timberville, Va. Window advertises meats, groceries, frozen foods, fruits. “Season’s Greetings” hand written on the negative. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0110; 4x5
- Front view of Timberville Department Store, under construction. Timberville, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0111; 2.5x3.5
- Front view of Timberville Department Store, under construction, alternate view. Timberville, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0112; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0112.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0112a; 2.5x3.5
- Front view of Timberville Department Store, under construction, alternate view. Timberville, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0113; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0113.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0113a; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0113.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0113b; 2.5x3.5
- A more up-close front view of Timberville Department Store, under construction. Timberville, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0114; 2.5x3.5
- Front view of Timberville Department Store, under construction, alternate view. Timberville, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0115; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0115.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0115a; 2.5x3.5
- Front view of Timberville Department Store, under construction, alternate view. Timberville, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0116; 2.5x3.5
- The main exhibit hall of Stroop’s Snake Farm, advertising snakes, alligators, a Siamese lamb, a 2-head calf, and a 4-legged chicken. Probably Edinburg, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0117; 2.5x3.5
- The main exhibit hall of Stroop’s Snake Farm, from an alternative angle. Probably Edinburg, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0118; 2.5x3.5
- Stroop’s Snake Farm, storefront view. Advertising reptiles and exotic birds. Probably Edinburg, Va. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0119; 4x5
- Stroop’s Snake Farm, storefront view, view from a distance across the street. Probably Edinburg, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0120; 4x5
- Stroop’s Snake Farm, storefront view, view from the side. Probably Edinburg, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0121; 4x5
- Inside of Stroop’s Snake Farm, view of cages with birds and other animals. Probably Edinburg, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0122; 4x5
- Inside of Stroop’s Snake Farm, view of a group of snakes of different sizes. Probably Edinburg, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0123; 4x5
- Snake in a box or cage. Stroop’s Snake Farm. Probably Edinburg, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0124; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0124.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0124a; 4x5
- Snake on a blanket outside. Stroop’s Snake Farm. Probably Edinburg, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0125; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0125.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0125a; 2.5x3.5
- Snake slithering on a blanket outside. Stroop’s Snake Farm. Probably Edinburg, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0126; 2.5x3.5
- Snake being handled over a blanket outside. Stroop’s Snake Farm. Probably Edinburg, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0127; 2.5x3.5
- Two men holding a large snake outside the front door of Stroop’s Snake Farm. Probably Edinburg, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0128; 2.5x3.5
- Two men sitting on the front steps of Stroop’s Snake Farm holding a large snake. Probably Edinburg, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0129; 2.5x3.5
- Inside of Stroop’s Snake Farm, a man handling a snake on the floor. Probably Edinburg, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0130; 2.5x3.5
- Inside of Stroop’s Snake Farm, a man handling a snake inside of its cage. Probably Edinburg, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0131; 2.5x3.5
- Inside of Stroop’s Snake Farm, a man holding a large snake. Probably Edinburg, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0132; 2.5x3.5
- Large group of small alligators inside of Stroop’s Snake Farm. Probably Edinburg, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0133; 4x5
- Group of small alligators inside of Stroop’s Snake Farm. Probably Edinburg, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0134; 4x5
- Bird perched atop a cage inside of Stroop’s Snake Farm. Probably Edinburg, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0135; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0136.
- Bird inside of its cage in Stroop’s Snake Farm. Probably Edinburg, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0136; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0135.
- Two birds inside of their cage at Stroop’s Snake Farm. Probably Edinburg, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0137; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0138.
- Bird perched atop a cage inside of Stroop’s Snake Farm. Probably Edinburg, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0138; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0137.
- Bird sitting on a swing inside its cage at Stroop’s Snake Farm. Probably Edinburg, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0139; 2.5x2.5
- Bird sitting atop a cage at Stroop’s Snake Farm. Probably Edinburg, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0140; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0141.
- Man with a bird on his shoulder inside of Stroop’s Snake Farm. Probably Edinburg, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0141; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0140.
- Inside of New Market Department Store, display of belts and belt buckles.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0142; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0142.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0142a; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0142.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0142b; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0142.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0142c; 4x5
- Inside of a bowling alley.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0143; 5x7
  See Oversize Negatives in Box 5, Folder 1.
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0143.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0143a; 5x7
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0143.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0143b; 5x7
- Inside of a bowling alley, a view from further back.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0144; 5x7
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0144.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0144a; 5x7
- Marston’s Home Appliance Store, view of two men pouring drinks in the window display.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0145; 2.5x2.5
- Marston’s Home Appliance Store, view of two men pouring drinks in the window display.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0001.01.0146; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0147.
- Marston’s Home Appliance Store, view of two men in the window display.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0001.01.0147; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0146.
- Orkney Springs Hotel, view from the side. Orkney Springs, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0148; 5x7
  Series 1c, “Buildings and Places: Hotels and Tourist Attractions” begins. See Oversize Negatives in Box 5, Folder 1.
- Orkney Springs Hotel, view from the opposite side. Orkney Springs, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0149; 5x7
- On the grounds of Orkney Springs Hotel, a place for church services or other gatherings. Wooden benches lined up facing a stone platform in the forest. Orkney Springs, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0150; 5x7
- On the grounds or drive to Orkney Springs Hotel, view of a windy mountain road. Orkney Springs, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0151; 5x7
- The Shenvalee Hotel and Golf Resort, front view. New Market, Va. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0152; 4x5
- The Shenvalee Hotel and Golf Resort, diagonal view of the front. New Market, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0153; 4x5
- The Shenvalee Hotel and Golf Resort, diagonal view of the front. New Market, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0154; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0154.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0154a; 4x5
- The Shenvalee Hotel and Golf Resort, distant view. New Market, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0155; 4x5
- Two women playing golf at the Shenvalee Hotel and Golf Resort, New Market, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0156; 2.5x3.5
- Two women playing golf at the Shenvalee Hotel and Golf Resort, New Market, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0157; 2.5x3.5
- Two women playing golf at the Shenvalee Hotel and Golf Resort, New Market, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0158; 2.5x3.5
- Two women playing golf at the Shenvalee Hotel and Golf Resort, New Market, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0159; 2.5x3.5
- A woman swinging a golf club at the Shenvalee Hotel and Golf Resort, New Market, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0160; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0160.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0160a; 2.5x3.5
- Two young boys in uniform, possibly boy scouts, at the Shenvalee Hotel and Golf Resort, New Market, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0161; 2.5x3.5
- The Lee-Jackson Hotel, front view. New Market, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0162; 4x5
- Inside the Lee-Jackson Hotel, view of the dining area. New Market, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0163; 4x5
- Inside the Lee-Jackson Hotel, view of the dining area. New Market, Va. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0164; 4x5
  Film is double exposed.
- Inside the Lee-Jackson Hotel, alternate view of the dining area. New Market, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0165; 4x5
- Inside the Lee-Jackson Hotel, view of the dining area, with a spinning wheel in the background. New Market, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0166; 4x5
- Shenandoah Alum Springs Hotel, view from the road. Orkney Springs, Va.Before 1948., Image: P0002.01.0167; 2.5x3.5
- Shenandoah Alum Springs Hotel, distant view from the road. Orkney Springs, Va.Before 1948., Image: P0002.01.0168; 2.5x3.5
- Shenandoah Alum Springs Hotel, view of one of the buildings. Orkney Springs, Va.Before 1948., Image: P0002.01.0169; 2.5x3.5
- Shenandoah Alum Springs Hotel, view of one of the smaller buildings with a bell tower. Orkney Springs, Va.Before 1948., Image: P0002.01.0170; 2.5x3.5
- Shenandoah Alum Springs Hotel, view of two of the buildings. Orkney Springs, Va.Before 1948., Image: P0002.01.0171; 2.5x3.5
- Shenandoah Alum Springs Hotel, alternate view. Orkney Springs, Va.Before 1948., Image: P0002.01.0172; 2.5x3.5
- Shenandoah Alum Springs Hotel, alternate view. Orkney Springs, Va.Before 1948., Image: P0002.01.0173; 2.5x3.5
- Shenandoah Alum Springs Hotel, distant view with two people walking towards it. Orkney Springs, Va.Before 1948., Image: P0002.01.0174; 2.5x3.5
- A man and a woman shaking hands on the steps of the Shenandoah Alum Springs Hotel, Orkney Springs, Va. Before 1948., Image: P0002.01.0175; 2.5x3.5
- A man and a woman shaking hands on the steps of the Shenandoah Alum Springs Hotel, alternate view. Orkney Springs, Va.Before 1948., Image: P0002.01.0176; 2.5x3.5
- A man and a woman standing next to a car at the steps of the Shenandoah Alum Springs Hotel. Orkney Springs, Va.Before 1948., Image: P0002.01.0177; 2.5x3.5
- Inside of the Shenandoah Alum Springs Hotel, a group of people sitting and standing, with a man playing a Jukebox. Orkney Springs, Va.Before 1948., Image: P0002.01.0178; 2.5x3.5
- Inside of the Shenandoah Alum Springs Hotel, a group of people socializing and dancing. Orkney Springs, Va.Before 1948., Image: P0002.01.0179; 2.5x3.5
- Inside of the Shenandoah Alum Springs Hotel, a group of people socializing and dancing. Orkney Springs, Va.Before 1948., Image: P0002.01.0180; 2.5x3.5
- Inside of the Shenandoah Alum Springs Hotel, a group of people reading, socializing, and playing the piano. Orkney Springs, Va.Before 1948., Image: P0002.01.0181; 2.5x3.5
- The swimming pool at the Shenandoah Alum Springs Hotel. Orkney Springs, Va.Before 1948., Image: P0002.01.0182; 2.5x3.5
- An alternate view of the swimming pool at the Shenandoah Alum Springs Hotel. Orkney Springs, Va.Before 1948., Image: P0002.01.0183; 2.5x3.5
- Four people sitting and standing on the edge of the swimming pool at the Shenandoah Alum Springs Hotel. Orkney Springs, Va.Before 1948., Image: P0002.01.0184; 2.5x3.5
- People sitting on the diving board of the swimming pool at the Shenandoah Alum Springs Hotel. Orkney Springs, Va.Before 1948., Image: P0002.01.0185; 2.5x3.5
- Someone diving into the swimming pool at the Shenandoah Alum Springs Hotel. Orkney Springs, Va.Before 1948., Image: P0002.01.0186; 2.5x3.5
- Man and woman standing on the side of the swimming pool at the Shenandoah Alum Springs Hotel. Orkney Springs, Va.Before 1948., Image: P0002.01.0187; 2.5x3.5
- Two people standing on the diving board of the swimming pool at the Shenandoah Alum Springs Hotel. Orkney Springs, Va.Before 1948., Image: P0002.01.0188; 2.5x3.5
- Inside the Shenandoah Alum Springs Hotel, view of the dining area. Orkney Springs, Va.Before 1948., Image: P0002.01.0189; 2.5x3.5
- Inside of the Shenandoah Alum Springs Hotel, view of the dining area. Orkney Springs, Va.Before 1948., Image: P0002.01.0190; 2.5x3.5
  Film is very faded.
- Small convenience store of sorts on the property of the Shenandoah Alum Springs Hotel. Orkney Springs, Va.Before 1948., Image: P0002.01.0191; 4x5
- Inside of the Shenandoah Alum Springs Hotel, possibly the convenience store. Orkney Springs, Va.Before 1948., Image: P0002.01.0192; 2.5x3.5
- Bryce’s Mountain Resort, close-up side view. Basye, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0193; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0194.
- Bryce’s Mountain Resort, side view. Basye, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0194; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0193.
- Bryce’s Mountain Resort, close-up of two men standing on the water wheel. Basye, Va. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0195; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0196.
- Bryce’s Mountain Resort, side view of two men standing on the water wheel. Basye, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0196; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0195.
- Bryce’s Mountain Resort, diagonal view. Basye, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0197; 2.5x2.5
- Bryce’s Mountain Resort, side view of two men standing on the water wheel. Basye, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0198; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0199.
- Bryce’s Mountain Resort, view from the ground of two men standing on the water wheel. Basye, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0199; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0198.
- Cottage Court/Will-O-Inn roadside cabins and service station, view from across the street. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0200; 4x5
- Outside view of a hotel or resort. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0201; 4x5
- Outside view of a hotel or resort. Location unknown.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0202; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0200.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0202a; 4x5
- Outside view of a hotel or resort. Location unknown.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0203; 5x7
- Outside view of a hotel or resort. Location unknown.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0204; 5x7
- Don’s Roadside Cabins, view from the side.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0205; 2.5x3.5
- Melrose Caverns, inside view. Rockingham County, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0206; 4x5
- Melrose Caverns, inside view. Rockingham County, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0207; 4x5
- Melrose Caverns, inside view. Rockingham County, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0208; 4x5
- Melrose Caverns, inside view. Rockingham County, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0209; 4x5
- Melrose Caverns, inside view. Rockingham County, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0210; 4x5
- Melrose Caverns, inside view. Rockingham County, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0211; 4x5
- Melrose Caverns, view of a face in the stone. Rockingham County, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0212; 4x5
- Melrose Caverns, inside view. Rockingham County, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0213; 4x5
- Melrose Caverns, inside view. Rockingham County, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0214; 4x5
- Melrose Caverns, inside view. Rockingham County, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0215; 4x5
- Endless Caverns, diagonal view of a building, possibly the welcome center or gift shop. New Market, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0216; 2.5x3.5
- Endless Caverns, outside of the cave entrance. New Market, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0217; 2.5x3.5
- Endless Caverns, outside of the welcome center/gift shop and cave entrance. New Market, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0218; 2.5x3.5
- Endless Caverns, outside of the cave entrance. New Market, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0219; 2.5x3.5
- Endless Caverns, outside of the cave entrance and welcome center/gift shop. New Market, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0220; 2.5x3.5
- Endless Caverns, view of the grounds. New Market, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0221; 2.5x3.5
- Endless Caverns, view of the cave entrance. New Market, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0222; 2.5x3.5
- Endless Caverns, view of the buildings on the grounds. New Market, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0223; 2.5x3.5
- Man standing behind a car labeled “Endless Caverns, New Market, Va.”c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0224; 2.5x3.5
- Endless Caverns, view of a dining area. New Market, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0225; 2.5x3.5